<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-04-22T15:23:54-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">DjangoCon US</title><subtitle>DjangoCon US 2022 conference will take place in San Diego, California
from October 16-21, 2022!
</subtitle><author><name>DjangoCon US</name></author><entry><title type="html">2019 Conference Wrap Up</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/Conference-Wrap-Up/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2019 Conference Wrap Up" /><published>2019-10-13T01:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-10-13T01:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/Conference-Wrap-Up</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/Conference-Wrap-Up/">&lt;p&gt;What an incredible year! DjangoCon US 2019 is officially over, but what an amazing ride. Thank you so much to each of the 400+ folks who attended this year. We had attendees, speakers, and sponsors from all over the world, and we are so thrilled to have such amazing representation from all the people that make up our community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DjangoCon US is a volunteer-run conference that succeeds because of the dedicated people who give up their lunches, nights, and weekends to tackle tasks small and large. We are very lucky to have so many organizers that see the value this conference brings to the tech world and are willing to donate their time to bring it to fruition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to the amazing teams we had running our media this year! The folks from AV101 were working long hours and were so accommodating. The women from White Coat Captioning were so kind and talented; the accuracy of their captioning was phenomenal. The women from ConFreaks were wonderful to work with and provided great suggestions on how we could make our video content better by being mindful of Q&amp;amp;A locations in each room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also want to give a special thanks to the speakers, tutorial presenters, and workshop hosts! We had over 400 attendees this year who were able to benefit from the time and effort put into all of the 2019 presentations. We were lucky enough to have talks that made us examine both the human and technology ecosystems, while still helping us learn and making us laugh. Keep an eye on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC0yY6a79pPY9J0ShIHRf6yw&quot;&gt;DjangoCon US YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt; to catch the ones you missed or to rewatch your favorites from this year and last.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, we want to thank our sponsors. Without their contributions, DjangoCon US would truly not be possible. Sponsorship funding is how we are able to bring people to the conference who might not otherwise be able to attend, provide food and fun to our attendees, hire amazing media folks to make sure our attendees and speakers have the best possible experience, and post talks to YouTube so that people in our community who are unable to attend can share in the learning. We were sponsored by so many companies that truly care about the DjangoCon community this year, and we are touched by their support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope that everyone had a wonderful year at DjangoCon US 2019, and we hope to see you all in 2021! Until then, consider checking out &lt;a href=&quot;http://bit.ly/dcus2019friends&quot;&gt;some conferences recommended and run by DjangoCon US 2019 attendees&lt;/a&gt;. Keep an eye on our &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/djangocon&quot;&gt;Twitter account&lt;/a&gt; for news about where we will be in 2021! If you would like to be part of the amazing organizing team that puts together DjangoCon US every year, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:hello@djangocon.us&quot;&gt;send us an email&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jessica Deaton</name></author><category term="General" /><summary type="html">What an incredible year! DjangoCon US 2019 is officially over, but what an amazing ride. Thank you so much to each of the 400+ folks who attended this year. We had attendees, speakers, and sponsors from all over the world, and we are so thrilled to have such amazing representation from all the people that make up our community.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">An Interview With Speaker Louise Grandjonc from the Azure Postgres Team</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/interview-with-louise-grandjonc-of-azure-postgres/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="An Interview With Speaker Louise Grandjonc from the Azure Postgres Team" /><published>2019-09-27T04:45:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-09-27T04:45:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/interview-with-louise-grandjonc-of-azure-postgres</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/interview-with-louise-grandjonc-of-azure-postgres/">&lt;p&gt;The week before DjangoCon US, Python developer and &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.microsoft.com/azure/postgresql/quickstart-create-server-database-portal&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;Azure Postgres engineer&lt;/a&gt; Louise Grandjonc (who joined Microsoft by way of the Citus Data acquisition) sat down for an interview with Claire Giordano. Louise explains technical topics in a way that makes sense—and she often uses unusual (and fun) examples, from crocodiles to owls, from Harry Potter to Taylor Swift. Here’s an edited transcript of Claire Giordano’s interview with Python developer and Postgres expert Louise Grandjonc (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/louisemeta&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;@louisemeta&lt;/a&gt;). Enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.citusdata.com/blog/2019/09/26/what-djangocon-has-to-do-with-postgres-and-crocodiles/&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;What DjangoCon has to do with Postgres and Crocodiles. An interview with Louise Grandjonc from Microsoft&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Heather Luna</name></author><category term="Sponsorship" /><summary type="html">The week before DjangoCon US, Python developer and Azure Postgres engineer Louise Grandjonc (who joined Microsoft by way of the Citus Data acquisition) sat down for an interview with Claire Giordano. Louise explains technical topics in a way that makes sense—and she often uses unusual (and fun) examples, from crocodiles to owls, from Harry Potter to Taylor Swift. Here’s an edited transcript of Claire Giordano’s interview with Python developer and Postgres expert Louise Grandjonc (@louisemeta). Enjoy.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Vinta - Managing Growth</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/vinta-growth/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vinta - Managing Growth" /><published>2019-09-25T06:38:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-09-25T06:38:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/vinta-growth</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/vinta-growth/">&lt;p&gt;Check out another Vinta blog post about how they have dealt with team growth!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vinta.com.br/blog/2019/managing-growing-team/&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;https://www.vinta.com.br/blog/2019/managing-growing-team/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Heather Luna</name></author><category term="Sponsorship" /><summary type="html">Check out another Vinta blog post about how they have dealt with team growth!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Vinta - Improving Code Review</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/vinta-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vinta - Improving Code Review" /><published>2019-09-25T05:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-09-25T05:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/vinta-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/vinta-blog/">&lt;p&gt;Check out Vinta’s blog around how they’ve improved their code reviewing process!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vinta.com.br/blog/2018/pull-requests-merging-good-practices-your-project-part-3/&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;https://www.vinta.com.br/blog/2018/pull-requests-merging-good-practices-your-project-part-3/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Heather Luna</name></author><category term="Sponsorship" /><summary type="html">Check out Vinta’s blog around how they’ve improved their code reviewing process!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Designing, Developing and Delivering a Django feature: How do we do it?</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/labcodes-djangodev/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Designing, Developing and Delivering a Django feature: How do we do it?" /><published>2019-09-24T06:52:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-09-24T06:52:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/labcodes-djangodev</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/labcodes-djangodev/">&lt;p&gt;Developing features the right way is hard. Most of the time, adding features with no criteria is going to make the software more complex, both for the users and for the developers working on it — and complexity is almost never good for business. Here at Labcodes one of our main goals is to help our clients understand the impact of every new feature on their user base. To make sure that new features don’t break the system or unnecessarily make it more complex, we use well established development and delivery processes, starting with design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we talk about design, we’re talking about surface level planning of the task, as well as its visual and coding. Before we start building any feature, we try to measure its real value for the final user. Through research, we understand which client profile will be the most impacted, which problem does the feature solve, how is the competition addressing the issue and what is the developing cost (time) for the sprint. Doing this before any execution steps guarantees that we’ll be focusing on the absolute musts, on the final user’s perspective, as well as prioritizing features by value delivered and time spent on the execution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all that research on our hands, we start prototyping and testing with users. At this moment, we make sure that whatever we understood from the research is spot on, and that the feature is clear and intuitive. This way, we don’t generate reworks, therefore saving money from our clients. After all, it is way faster to redo a prototype after a feedback then to change something from a software. With the feature validated, we proceed to the definitive design, and the feature is ready to be coded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every piece of software we make is thoroughly tested. We understand that these tests are the first design feedback from our code, and, like any other feedback, the sooner we have them, the better. We follow the best procedures, that guarantee the internal and external quality of the product, making it ready to be futher implemented and scaled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But our job isn’t done when the feature is delivered. We establish metrics to evaluate how these features are being used, and we have an efficient analysis of all of our delivery pipeline. This way, we generate more data, empowering our future decisions, whether about what is the next feature we should work on, or about the value said feature would have for the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you think about the way we make software? Do not hesitate in sending us an e-mail &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:contact@labcodes.com.br&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;contact@labcodes.com.br&lt;/a&gt;, or talking to us anywhere in the event. We’ll be having three different talks throughout DjangoCon and we’re always open to sharing knowledge. We hope to see you soon and thanks for the attention!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Heather Luna</name></author><category term="Sponsorship" /><summary type="html">Developing features the right way is hard. Most of the time, adding features with no criteria is going to make the software more complex, both for the users and for the developers working on it — and complexity is almost never good for business. Here at Labcodes one of our main goals is to help our clients understand the impact of every new feature on their user base. To make sure that new features don’t break the system or unnecessarily make it more complex, we use well established development and delivery processes, starting with design.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Come Meet Microsoft at DjangoCon US 2019</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/microsoft-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Come Meet Microsoft at DjangoCon US 2019" /><published>2019-09-24T06:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-09-24T06:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/microsoft-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/microsoft-blog/">&lt;p&gt;Check out Microsoft’s blog post and stop by their booth!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/come-meet-microsoft-at-djangocon-2019/&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/come-meet-microsoft-at-djangocon-2019/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Heather Luna</name></author><category term="Sponsorship" /><summary type="html">Check out Microsoft’s blog post and stop by their booth!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Social Events at DjangoCon US</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/social-events/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Social Events at DjangoCon US" /><published>2019-09-20T01:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-09-20T01:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/social-events</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/social-events/">&lt;p&gt;We’re so excited to tell you about your opportunities to socialize with and get to know other attendees, speakers, organizers, and sponsors!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;opening-reception&quot;&gt;Opening Reception&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: 6:30-8:00 pm, Monday, September 23&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: West Lawn at the Marriott (on the other side of the pool from the Marriott restaurant)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&lt;/strong&gt;: Join us for some food and non-alcoholic drinks to relax after the first day of talks! We’ll have a mac and cheese station, a slider bar, and other tasty snacks for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;board-game-night&quot;&gt;Board Game Night&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: 6:00-10:00 pm, Tuesday, September 24&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: Salon A-E&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&lt;/strong&gt;: Get together with other Djangonauts for board games and camaraderie. We’ll have some games on hand, but feel free to bring your favorites!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sponsor-events&quot;&gt;Sponsor Events&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;mini-golf-with-caktus&quot;&gt;Mini-Golf with Caktus&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: 7:00 pm, Wednesday, September 25&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: Tiki Town Adventure Golf (3114 Mission Blvd, San Diego)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&lt;/strong&gt;: Play a round of mini-golf on Caktus! &lt;a href=&quot;/news/caktus-blog-1/&quot;&gt;RSVP and get more information here&lt;/a&gt;, and note that this event might reach capacity.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Lacey Williams Henschel</name></author><category term="General" /><summary type="html">We’re so excited to tell you about your opportunities to socialize with and get to know other attendees, speakers, organizers, and sponsors!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/blog/opening_reception.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/blog/opening_reception.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Tito &amp;amp; DjangoCon US</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/tito-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tito &amp;amp; DjangoCon US" /><published>2019-09-18T20:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-09-18T20:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/tito-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/tito-blog/">&lt;p&gt;One of the big benefits of working at Tito is getting to see the amazing events and conferences our customers and partners bring to their industries, and DjangoCon US is a shining example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the words of our Chief Commercial Officer, Karl McCarthy, “DjangoCon encapsulates all that is good with community-run tech events and it’s fantastic to see all the hard work pay off for the DjangoCon team.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever hosted an event like this, or even been to one, you’ll know what he’s talking about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such, we were more than happy to continue our partnership with DjangoCon US this year and were thrilled when the team offered to let us tell you a little bit about the work we do at Tito.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tito is &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/features&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;simple, powerful event software&lt;/a&gt;. We’ve been fortunate enough to work with events in over &lt;a href=&quot;https://ti.to/about&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;2,500 cities so far&lt;/a&gt;, many of them run by — and run for — developers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We aim to provide a simple-to-use yet robust tool to sell tickets and manage events online, with some special parts added in to make the experience that bit more enjoyable than usual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The timing couldn’t be better to write up a piece like this, honestly. We’ve spent a lot of this year thinking about what makes “Tito” Tito. Of course, it comes down to customers like DjangoCon US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We make the software, but our customers and their attendees create the amazing experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We settled on three guiding values to help us on our continued journey building the company, the product, and our ability to keep working with some of the most creative and dedicated people you’re likely to ever come across.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout that process, we realised that we want to focus on the principles of integrity, excellence, and delight. You can read more about how those values &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.tito.io/posts/the-value-of-integrity/&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;guide our product decisions and business decisions&lt;/a&gt; on our site. And here you can see &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/f5fRBZykYA8&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;the Tito product in action&lt;/a&gt;, if you’d like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that’s left to say is a hearty congratulations to the organising team behind DjangoCon US and to you for the delightful time you’re due to have at their events. If you’d like to get in touch with anyone at Tito should you be interested in learning more, you can find us at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sales@tito.io&quot; rel=&quot;sponsored&quot;&gt;sales@tito.io&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Heather Luna</name></author><category term="Sponsorship" /><summary type="html">One of the big benefits of working at Tito is getting to see the amazing events and conferences our customers and partners bring to their industries, and DjangoCon US is a shining example.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/social/avatar-main.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Help Run DjangoCon US</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/volunteer-opportunities/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Help Run DjangoCon US" /><published>2019-09-14T01:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-09-14T01:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/volunteer-opportunities</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/volunteer-opportunities/">&lt;p&gt;We have a wide variety of volunteer slots available! If you’d like to sign up for one (or more) we have a &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1VO8Xh6xPOQb32WjUD7pKJCMXvqCdcMz95CqIoNToUsA/edit#gid=0&quot;&gt;handy spreadsheet&lt;/a&gt;. Here’s more information on each role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;session-chairs&quot;&gt;Session Chairs&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session chairs&lt;/strong&gt; help foster a supportive environment by welcoming guests, introducing speakers, and making sure folks get to where they need to be. You are the moderator of the session. You’ll arrive in the room where the talks on your schedule take place 10 minutes before the talk starts. Meet your speaker and find out a few things: how do you pronounce your name? Do you want to take questions? How do you want us to count down time? There will be a handy questionnaire on your clipboard to assist with this. At showtime, you’ll introduce the speaker to the audience, keeping it simple — their name, where they’re from, and talk title. During the talk, watch the clock and let the speaker know how much time they have left before questions (show signs at the -15, -10 and -5 mark). Mediate questions (if any), and let the speaker and attendees know when it’s time to wrap it all up. After that, help the speaker disconnect the microphone and make any announcements. There will be a session manager checking in to support you throughout your shift.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;swag-bag-stuffing&quot;&gt;Swag Bag Stuffing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll be stuffing swag bags for everyone on Sunday afternoon! If you’ll be around and not in a tutorial, we’d appreciate your help. The more people we have, the faster it will go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;registration-desk&quot;&gt;Registration Desk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll need people at the registration desk to check people into the conference and help answer questions. Shifts are one hour long, and you’ll always have a partner working with you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sprint-mentors-volunteers-and-git-help-desk&quot;&gt;Sprint Mentors, Volunteers, and Git Help Desk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sign up to help mentor or run errands at the sprints. For this volunteer opportunity, you just need to be willing to help newcomers to the sprints make their first commits!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Git Help Desk will help Git newbies make their first PRs and free up the sprint mentors for questions about the sprint projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1VO8Xh6xPOQb32WjUD7pKJCMXvqCdcMz95CqIoNToUsA/edit#gid=0&quot;&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Rebecca Kindschi</name></author><category term="General" /><summary type="html">We have a wide variety of volunteer slots available! If you’d like to sign up for one (or more) we have a handy spreadsheet. Here’s more information on each role.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/blog/volunteer-opportunities-2019.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/blog/volunteer-opportunities-2019.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">It’s my first DjangoCon US. What should I bring?</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/first-time-things-to-bring/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It’s my first DjangoCon US. What should I bring?" /><published>2019-09-14T01:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-09-14T01:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/first-time-things-to-bring</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:8000/news/first-time-things-to-bring/">&lt;p&gt;It’s your first DjangoCon US (or maybe even your first tech conference). Are you concerned about what you should pack?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I (Drew Winstel, the 2019 Opportunity Grants chair) was in that position two years ago at DjangoCon US 2017 in Spokane, WA.  Here’s what I think you should pack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;notepad-and-penpencil-or-a-laptop-and-charger&quot;&gt;Notepad and pen/pencil, or a laptop and charger&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you like your notes a bit more analog? A notepad is exactly what you need. Many people like to leave their laptops in their rooms entirely during talks and take notes on paper instead. Plus, it’s great for logging contact info of people you meet if you don’t have the time or patience to log their contact info into your phone’s contacts immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can’t live without your laptop, make sure you bring your charging cable. There’s ample Wi-Fi at the conference provided by the Marriott, so you’ll have the internet at your disposal. Many attendees will have their laptops open to take notes, follow along with slides, and/or test out the concepts being presented during talks. Plus, it’s much easier to live-tweet talks from your computer than your phone if you’re into that sort of thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;refillable-water-bottle-andor-coffee-cup&quot;&gt;Refillable water bottle and/or coffee cup&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s pretty annoying getting thirsty in the middle of a conference talk. The Marriott provides water dispensers in the hotel lobby, each of the conference rooms, the green room, and the Rio Vista Pavilion, so there are ample opportunities to keep yourself hydrated. Plus, you can be greener by reusing your own vessel instead of single-use disposable cups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are coffee and tea in the Rio Vista Pavilion as well, so if you’re a coffee/tea drinker, bring your own tumbler if you want extra for the talks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;comfortable-clothes&quot;&gt;Comfortable clothes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone is welcome, and dress casually and comfortably, whether that’s shorts, pants, a dress, or whatever makes you feel good. It’s up to you to decide what you would like to wear. As long as it isn’t a Code of Conduct violation, it’s pretty much up to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the rooms can get a bit chilly, so you might want to have a jacket or sweater handy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cell-phone&quot;&gt;Cell phone&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s practically essential for survival in suburban America. The mobile coverage is great in the venue area for all four major providers, so about any device will work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sunglasses-and-sunscreen&quot;&gt;Sunglasses and sunscreen&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s San Diego, California. It’s going to be warm and sunny. Preliminary forecasts show no meaningful chances of rain between the time I wrote this post and the tutorial day, with highs around 75-80 °F (24-27 °C) and lows around 65-68 °F (18-20 °C). There’s quite a bit of outdoor space to relax at the Marriott, and the walk between the conference rooms and the Rio Vista Pavilion (where breakfast and lunch are served) involves a brief outdoor trip across some bright concrete. Plus, there are lots of outdoor tables for eating under the sun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;snacks&quot;&gt;Snacks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Marriott will have breakfast, lunch, and snacks during the breaks (11:00 AM and 3:40 PM on main talk days) on all conference days as well as appetizers for the opening party on Monday. If you’re an early riser like me, you’ll probably want a snack before breakfast (8:30 AM on Monday, 9:00 AM Tuesday and Wednesday). Also, if you have special dietary needs, it can’t hurt to have a spare snack on hand just in case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;exercise-clothes&quot;&gt;Exercise clothes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before or after a long day of conference talks, I like to at least get a brief workout in. The hotel has some exercise machines indoors and outside on the pool deck, which is a refreshing way to unwind while catching up on my favorite podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;swimsuit&quot;&gt;Swimsuit&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hotel has a nice pool and hot tub in the courtyard. While outdoor temperatures may be a bit cool for most of us to enjoy the pool, the hot tub gets lots of use after a day of sitting in meeting room chairs. It’s open until 11 PM every night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;thanks&quot;&gt;Thanks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Obidecoque&quot;&gt;@Obidecoque&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Obidecoque/status/1172588365864218624&quot;&gt;inspiring&lt;/a&gt; this post and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Rachell_Calhoun&quot;&gt;@Rachell_Calhoun&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Rachell_Calhoun/status/1175117174509375488&quot;&gt;suggesting&lt;/a&gt; refillable coffee mugs.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Drew Winstel</name></author><category term="General" /><summary type="html">It’s your first DjangoCon US (or maybe even your first tech conference). Are you concerned about what you should pack?</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/blog/what-should-i-bring.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:8000/static/img/blog/what-should-i-bring.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>